A Guide to the Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Committee Records, 1953-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Board of Visitors of the University of Virginia, Committee Records 1953-2000
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-1/1/3.381
This collection consists of 20,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library from the Board of Visitors 2000 November 30.
Scope and Content Information
The records of the commitees of the Board of Visitors, chiefly minutes of meetings and correspondence. Also included are some ad hoc committees and some special committees; however, most special committees (i.e. nominating committees) are accessioned separately.
Committees are: the Finance Committee, Buildings and Grounds Committee, Student Affairs and Athletics Committee, Educational Policy Committee, Health Affairs Committee, External Affairs Committee, the Audit Committee, and The University of Virginia's College at Wise Committee.
Contents List
- Administrative Committee 1953-1954 (Box 1)
- Administrative Organization Committee 1954-1955 (Box 1)
- Alumni Affairs, Special Committee on 1990-1991 (Box 1)
- Alumni Organization's to Board (Correspondence), ad hoc Committee on Relationship of 1978 Jan-1979 Feb (Box 1)
- Alumni Organization's to Board of Visitors--Minutes, ad hoc Committee on Relationship of 1978 Jan-1979 Jan (Box 1)
- Alston's Appeal--ad hoc Committee 1998 (Box 1)
- Athletics 1967-1975 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee (2 folders) 1980-1981 (Box 1)
- Audit Committee--Minutes 1980 May-1983 May (Box 1)
- Audit Committee (6 folders) 1982-1986 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1983-1986 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting (1 of 7) 1984 May 31 (Box 2)
- Audit Committee Meeting (2-7 of 7) 1984-1985 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee--Reports (3 folders) 1982-1985 (Box 3)
- Audit Committee--Reports (2 folders) 1985-1990 (Box 4)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume I) 1986 Jan 30 (Box 4)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1986 Jan 30 (Box 4)
- Audit Committee Meeting (3 folders) 1986 (Box 4)
- Audit Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1986-1987 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume I) 1987 Jan 29 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1987 Jan 29 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1987 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting (2 folders) 1987-1988 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Minutes 1987 Oct-1988 May (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1988 Jan 21 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1988 Jan 21 (Box 5)
- Audit Committee Meeting (2 folders) 1988 (Box 6)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1988 Dec 29 (Box 6)
- Audit Committee Meeting (3 folders) 1989 (Box 6)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1989-1991 (Box 6)
- Audit Committee Meeting (3 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 6)
- Audit Committee--Correspondence 1991 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Meeting (2 folders) 1991 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume I) 1991 Oct 3 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Meeting (Volume II) 1991 Oct 3 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Meeting (4 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1992-1993 (Box 7)
- Audit Committee Meeting (3 folders) 1993 (Box 8)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1993-1994 (Box 8)
- Audit Committee Minutes (3 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 8)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1994 (Box 8)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1994 Feb 4 (Box 8)
- Audit Committee Meeting 1994 Jun 10 (Box 9)
- Audit Committee Correspondence 1995 (Box 9)
- Audit Committee Meeting (3 folders) 1995 (Box 9)
- Audit Committee Minutes 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 9)
- Audit Committee-Correspondence (3 folders) 1996-1998 (Box 10)
- Audit Committee-Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 10)
- Blandy Farm Committee 1965-1976 (Box 10)
- Birdwood Report--A Residential College Plan 1978-1979 (Box 10)
- Board of Visitors--Board Committee Records 1988 Apr 13 (Box 10)
- Board as Committee of the Whole--Minutes (3 folders) 1991-1993 (Box 10)
- Board as a Committee of the Whole--Board of Visitors 1992 Oct-1993 Jun (Box 10)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (1) 1959-1971 (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1960-1964 (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee 1961 Jan-Oct (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes (5 folders) 1965-1973 (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1972-1975 (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes (5 folders) 1973-1978 (Box 11)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1977-1979 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1978 Aug-1979 Jun (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee (2 folders) 1979-1981 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1981 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1981 Oct-1982 Jun (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee 1982 Jan-1983 Mar (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1982 Sept-1983 Jun (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee 1983 Apr (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1983-1984 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee 1983 May-1984 Nov (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 12)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee 1985 Oct-1987 May (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1987 Oct-1988 May (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1988-1989 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1990 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1990-1991 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1991 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1992 (Box 13)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1992-1993 (Box 14)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1992 Jul 9-1993 Jun 29 (Box 14)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1993 (Box 14)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1993-1994 (Box 14)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (1 of 2) 1994 (Box 14)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (2 of 2) 1994 (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1994-1995 (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1995 (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1995 Jun-1977 Jun (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence 1996 (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (1 of 3) 1997-1998 (Box 15)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Correspondence (2-3 of 3) 1997-1998 (Box 16)
- Buildings and Grounds Committee Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 16)
- Campaign Organizing Committee 1980-1985 (Box 16)
- Cavalier Daily Appeal, Special Meeting to hear the 1929 (Box 16)
- Cavalier Daily Correspondence 1979-1980 (Box 16)
- Chapel Committee (2 folders) 1960-1978 (Box 16)
- Clinch Valley College (1 of 2) 1989-1993 (Box 16)
- Clinch Valley College (2 of 2) 1986-1989 (Box 17)
- Clinch Valley College, Special Committee on--Minutes 1992-1994 (Box 17)
- Clinch Valley College, Special Committee on 1993 Apr-1996 Jun (Box 17)
- Clinch Valley College--Correspondence 1995 (Box 17)
- Clinch Valley Special Committee--Correspondence 1996-1998 (Box 17)
- Clinch Valley Special Committee--Minutes 1997-1999 (Box 17)
- Commencement and Convocation, Committee on (2 folders) 1981-1985 (Box 17)
- Commencement and Convocation--Committee 1986-1988 (Box 17)
- Commencement and Convocation--Committee 1988-1989 (Box 18)
- Committee Agenda (4 folders) 1981-1992 (Box 18)
- Committees 1964-1971 (Box 18)
- Committees (6 folders) 1972-1995 (Box 18)
- Contractual Relations, Committee on 1969 January 24 (Box 18)
- Dean Harris' Committee, General Records, ad hoc Committee 1968-1969 (Box 19)
- Disruptive Practices, Special Committee on (2 folders) 1970 (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1963-1968 (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1963-1970 (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1967 Oct-1969 Jun (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (copy 1) 1969 (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (copy 2) 1969 (Box 19)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (copy 3) 1969 (Box 19)
- Education Policy Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1970-1972 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1971-1975 (Box 20)
- Education Policy Committee Minutes (5 folders) 1972-1977 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1976-1979 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee of the Board--Minutes 1977 Sept 14-1978 Jun 1 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1978-1980 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee 1980 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1980 Oct-1981 Jun (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee 1981-1982 (Box 20)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (3 folders) 1981-1984 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee 1983-1984 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1985-1986 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee 1985 Oct-1987 May (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1987 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1987-1989 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1988-1989 (Box 21)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence (3 folders) 1990 (Box 22)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 22)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1991 (Box 22)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1991-1993 (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1993 (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1994-1995 (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 23)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence 1996 (Box 24)
- Educational Policy Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1997-1999 (Box 24)
- Educational Policy Committee--Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 24)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1963 (Box 24)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1963-1967 (Box 25)
- Executive Committee Correspondence (3 folders) 1964-1978 (Box 25)
- Executive Committee Minutes (4 folders) 1969-1977 (Box 25)
- Executive Committee--General Counsel 1974-1988 (Box 25)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1977 Jul 1-1980 May 5 (Box 25)
- Executive Committee (2 folders) 1979-1981 (Box 26)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1980 Jul-1981 Apr (Box 26)
- Executive Committee 1981 Sept-Dec (Box 26)
- Executive Committee Minutes (3 folders) 1981-1985 (Box 26)
- Executive Committee (3 folders) 1984-1985 (Box 26)
- Executive Committee 1985 Jan (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Correspondence 1988 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1985 Aug-1988 Jul (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Correspondence 1986-1987 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee--William H. Muller, Jr. 1989 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Correspondence 1991-1992 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1993-1997 (Box 27)
- Executive Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 28)
- Executive Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1997-1999 (Box 28)
- Executive Committee Minutes 1997-1999 (Box 28)
- Executive Session Items 1996-1997 (Box 28)
- Executive Summaries 1997-2000 (Box 29)
- External Affairs, Special Committee on 1990 Mar 30 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee 1992 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1992 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Minutes 1992 Oct-1993 Jun (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1993 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee 1993-1994 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1994 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Minutes 1994-1995 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1995 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1996 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1997-1998 (Box 29)
- External Affairs Committee-Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 30)
- Finance Committee (3 folders) 1953-1960 (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1961-1968 (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1962-1967 (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1967 Oct-1969 Jun (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1970 Oct-1971 Jun (Box 30)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (3 folders) 1970-1977 (Box 31)
- Finance Committee Minutes (6 folders) 1971-1977 (Box 31)
- Finance Committee of the Board, Minutes of the 1977 Jul 18-1978 Jun 2 (Box 32)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1978-1979 (Box 32)
- Finance Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1978-1980 (Box 32)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (1 of 2) 1980-1981 (Box 32)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 of 2) 1980-1981 (Box 33)
- Finance Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1980-1982 (Box 33)
- Finance Committee 1982 (Box 33)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1982 Sept-1983 June (Box 33)
- Finance Committee (3 folders) 1983 (Box 33)
- Finance Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1983-1985 (Box 33)
- Finance Committee (7 folders) 1984-1987 (Box 34)
- Finance Committee (1 of 2) 1986-1988 (Box 34)
- Finance Committee (2 of 2) 1986-1988 (Box 35)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (5 folders) 1985-1987 (Box 35)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1987 Aug-1988 May (Box 35)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (1 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 35)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 of 2) 1988-1989 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee 1988 Dec 1 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Meeting 1989 May 9 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1990 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1990 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1990-1991 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee 1990 Apr 19 (Box 36)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1991 (Box 37)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1992 (Box 37)
- Finance Committee Correspondence 1992-1993 (Box 37)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1992 Oct-1993 Jun (Box 37)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1993 (Box 37)
- Finance Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1993-1995 (Box 38)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (3 folders) 1995 (Box 38)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 38)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (1 of 2) 1996 (Box 38)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 of 2) 1996 (Box 39)
- Finance Committee (2 folders) 1997 (Box 39)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (1 of 2) 1997 (Box 39)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (2 of 2) 1997 (Box 40)
- Finance Committee Correspondence (3 folders) 1998 (Box 40)
- Finance Committee Minutes 1997-1999 (Box 40)
- Fraternity or Sorority Housing Proposal 1983 (Box 41)
- Fraternity and Sorority Housing, Special Committee on (3 folders) 1983-1985 (Box 41)
- Future, Committee on 1972 (Box 41)
- Future of the University, Committee on 1988-1990 (Box 41)
- Future Fundraising Coordination of Alumni Association, Committee on 1989 (Box 41)
- Governmental Affairs, Special Committee on 1990-1991 (Box 41)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence 1971 Jan-1977 Oct (Box 41)
- Health Affairs Committee--Minutes 1976-1977 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee of the Board-Minutes 1977 Oct 8-1978 Jun 1 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee 1978-1979 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes 1978 Oct-1979 Jun (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee (2 folders) 1979-1984 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes (5 folders) 1980-1985 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee 1985 Oct-1987 May (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (1 of 2) 1985-1986 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (2 of 2) 1987 (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee--Minutes 1987 Oct-1988 May (Box 42)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes (3 folders) 1988-1991 (Box 43)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1991-1992 (Box 43)
- Health Affairs Committee 1992 Oct-1993 Jun (Box 43)
- Health Affairs Committee - Correspondence 1993 (Box 43)
- Health Affairs Committee Executive Session 1993 (Box 44)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes 1993-1994 (Box 44)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes 1994-1995 (Box 44)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (4 folders) 1995 (Box 44)
- Health Affairs Committee Correspondence (2 folders) 1995 (Box 45)
- Health Affairs Committee Minutes 1995 Jun-1997 Jun (Box 45)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1996 (Box 45)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (1 of 2 folders) 1996-1997 (Box 45)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (2 of 2 folders) 1996-1997 (Box 46)
- Health Affairs Committee--Correspondence (1 of 2 folders) 1997-1998 (Box 46)
- Health Affairs Committee-Correspondence (2 of 2 folders) 1997-1998 (Box 46)
- Health Affairs Committee--Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 46)
- Health Sciences Committee Correspondence 1961-1970 (Box 46)
- Health Sciences Committee Minutes 1972 Dec-1973 May (Box 46)
- Health Sciences Committee 1973 Jul 31-1974 May 16 (Box 47)
- Health Sciences Committee Minutes (2 folders) 1974-1976 (Box 47)
- Honor System, Board of Visitors ad hoc Committees--Special Committee on the Status of the (2 folders) 1977-1984 (Box 47)
- Honor System, Special Committee on the status of the 1977-1984 (Box 47)
- Inter-Group Relations, Special Committee on 1990-1993 (Box 47)
- Investment Banker Selection Committee 1983 (Box 47)
- Investment Subcommittee Correspondence (1-2 of 5) 1993-1997 (Box 47)
- Investment Subcommittee Correspondence (3-5 of 5) 1994 (Box 48)
- Investment Subcommittee Minutes 1995 Jun-1997 Jan (Box 48)
- Investment Management Co.--UVA Correspondence 1998 (Box 48)
- Investment Subcommittee-Correspondence (1 of 3) 1996-1998 (Box 48)
- Investment Subcommittee--Correspondence (2-3 of 3) 1996-1998 (Box 49)
- Investment Subcommittee--Minutes 1997-2000 (Box 49)
- Land Committee (2 folders) 1954-1957 (Box 49)
- Lawn, Committee to Develop Policies for the Use of the 1986-1988 (Box 49)
- Library Correspondence/Minutes, Special Committee on the 1971 Nov-1973 Apr (Box 49)
- Libraries, Special Committee on--Correspondence 1991 (Box 49)
- Libraries, Special Committee on--Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 49)
- Long Range Planning Committee 1961 April (Box 49)
- Long Range Planning Committee--Parking Subcommittee Reports (1 of 3) 1961 Apr-Jun (Box 49)
- Long Range Planning Committee--Parking Subcommittee Reports (2-3 of 3) 1961 Apr-Jun (Box 50)
- Manual Committee 1963-1966 (Box 50)
- Manual Committee Minutes 1963-1966 (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee--Minutes 1961-1968 (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee Correspondence 1961-1971 (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee 1963-1978 (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee--Minutes 1967 Oct-1969 Jun (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee 1970 Oct-1971 Jun (Box 50)
- Mary Washington College Committee--Minutes 1970-1972 (Box 51)
- Mary Washington College Committee 1971 Sept 30-1972 May 31 (Box 51)
- Medical Committee 1953-1955 (Box 51)
- Medical Committee (2 folders) 1956-1958 (Box 51)
- Medical Committee Minutes (3 folders) 1963-1971 (Box 51)
- Medical Committee 1971 Sept 30-1972 June 1 (Box 51)
- Medical Center Council of Trustees Committee 1986-1988 (Box 51)
- Membership--Directory Correspondence 1966-1985 (Box 52)
- Nuclear Reactor--ad hoc Committee 1998 (Box 52)
- Page-Barbour Committee 1959-1960 (Box 52)
- President's Compensation Committee 1964 (Box 52)
- Presidential Selection, Special Committee to Study the Process 1990 (Box 52)
- Procedures for Selecting Faculty Members, Special Committee 1965 (Box 52)
- Public Occasions Committee (2 folders) 1976-1980 (Box 52)
- Real-Estate, Special Committee of the BOV (2 folders) 1985-1986 (Box 52)
- Real Estate Foundation, University of Virginia 1986 (Box 52)
- Rector and Committee Chairs--Minutes 1994 Nov 30 (Box 52)
- Relations between Board and Student Body, Special Committee to Study 1976-1978 (Box 53)
- Rotunda Policy Committee 1986-1989 (Box 53)
- Scholarship Committee 1952-1955 (Box 53)
- Self Study (Steering) Committee 1985 (Box 53)
- Senate Committee 1971-1972 (Box 53)
- Senate Finance Committee 1969 Oct-Nov (Box 53)
- Special Organizational Study Committee Correspondence 1965-1967 (Box 53)
- Special Recognition, Committee on 1964-1967 (Box 53)
- Special Recognition, Committee on (Materials from other Universities) 1968 June 8 (Box 53)
- Standing Committees--Volume 1926-1928 (Box 53)
- Strike Committee 1970 (Box 53)
- Student Activities Committee (2 folders) 1958-1972 (Box 53)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (1 of 3) 1949-1954 (Box 53)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (2-3 of 3) 1949-1954 (Box 54)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1959-1966 (Box 54)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1962-1969 (Box 54)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence (2 folders) 1969-1970 (Box 54)
- Student Affairs and Athletic Committee Minutes 1970 Oct-1971 Jun (Box 54)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee-Minutes 1971-1977 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1971 Sept 30-1977 June 1 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletic Committee Minutes 1972 Oct-1973 May (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1973 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1973 July 31-1974 May 16 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletic Committee Minutes 1974 Oct-1975 May (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee-Correspondence (3 folders) 1974-1977 (Box 55)
- Student Affairs and Athletic Committee Minutes (3 folders) 1975 Oct-1978 (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1978 (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee-Minutes 1978 Oct-1979 Jun (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1979 (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (3 folders) 1979 Apr (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1979 Oct-1980 Jun (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1980 (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1980 Oct-1981 Jun (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1981 Jan-1882 Jul (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1981 Oct-1982 Jun (Box 56)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee 1982 Sept-Dec (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1982-1984 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (2 folders) 1983 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1984-1985 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee (2 folders) 1984-1987 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1985-1987 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1988 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1988-1990 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes (2 folders) 1990-1991 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1991 (Box 57)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1991-1992 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1992 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1992 Oct-1993 Jun (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1993 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1993-1994 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Correspondence 1994 (Box 58)
- Student Affairs and Athletics Committee--Minutes 1994-1995 (Box 58)